Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Central Region Freight Joint Area Committee Transcript Records 1954-2010 IBT0053
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1967, March 21-22 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1967, March 21-22 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Meeting [1 of 2], 1967, March 21-22 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Meeting [2 of 2], 1967, March 21-22 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Joint Steel Meeting, 1967, March 21-22 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Transamerican Cases Meeting, 1967, March 22 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Western Cases Meeting, 1967, March 22 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Special Council Meeting, 1967, April 21 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Special Council Meeting, 1967, April 21 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Special Council Meeting, 1967, April 21 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Union Negotiations Meeting, 1967, May 4 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Council Meeting, 1967, June 12 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1967, June 13-14 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1967, June 13-14 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1967, June 13-14 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Meeting [1 of 2], 1967, June 13-14 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Meeting [2 of 2], 1967, June 13-14 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Transamerican Cases Meeting, 1967, June 14 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1967, June 13-15 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1967, June 13-15 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Case #222 Council Meeting, 1967, June 13-15 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1967, June 13-15 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1967, June 13-15 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Council Meeting, 1967, September 18 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1967, September 19 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1967, September 19 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1967, September 19 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1967, September 19-20 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1967, September 19-20 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Transamerican Cases Meeting, 1967, September 20 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1967, September 19-21 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1967, September 19-21 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1967, September 19-21 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1967, September 19-21 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1967, September 19-21 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Transamerican Cases Report, 1967, December (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Council Meeting, 1967, December 11 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1967, December 12-13 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1967, December 12-13 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Transamerican Cases Meeting, 1967, December 13 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting, 1967, December 12-13 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1967, December 12-13 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1967, December 12-13 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1967, December 12-13 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1967, December 12-13 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1967, December 12-13 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1967, December 12-13 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Misc. Letters, 1968, January-February (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Council Meeting, 1968, March 18 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1968, March 19-20 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1968, March 19-20 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1968, March 19-20 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1968, March 19-20 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [1 of 2], 1968, March 19-20 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [2 of 2], 1968, March 19-20 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1968, March 19-20 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1968, March 19-20 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1968, March 20 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Transamerican Cases Meeting, 1968, March 20 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Joint Steel & Special Sub-Committee Meeting, 1968, April 22 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1968, April 22 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Council Meeting, 1968, June 10 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Rider Committee Meeting, 1968, June 10 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting, 1968, June 11 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1968, June 11 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1968, June 11 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1968, June 11 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1968, June 11-12 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1968, June 11-12 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Transamerican Cases Committee Meeting, 1968, June 12 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1968, June 11-13 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1968, June 11-13 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1968, June 11-13 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1968, June 11-13 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Paul Woosley Time Cards, 1968, August 31 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Council Meeting, 1968, September 23 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1968, September 24 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting, 1968, September 24 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1968, September 24 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1968, September 24 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1968, September 24-25 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1968, September 24-25 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1968, September 24-25 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1968, September 24-25 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1968, September 24-25 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Transamerican Cases Committee Meeting, 1968, September 25 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Council Meeting, 1968, December 16 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting, 1968, December 17 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1968, December 17 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1968, December 17-18 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1968, December 17-18 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1968, December 17-18 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1968, December 17-18 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1968, December 17-18 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1968, December 18 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Council Meeting, 1969, March 10 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1969, March 10-12 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1969, March 10-12 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1969, March 11-12 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1969, March 11-12 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Transamerican Cases Meeting, 1969, March 12 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1969, March 11-12 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1969, March 11-12 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1969, March 11-12 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1969, March 11-12 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Council Meeting, 1969, June 9 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Committee Meeting, 1969, June 10 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1969, June 10-11 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1969, June 10-11 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1969, June 10-11 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1969, June 10-11 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1969, June 10-11 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1969, June 10-11 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Special Subcommittee Meeting, 1969, June 11 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Transamerican and Western Cases Meeting, 1969, June 11 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1969, July 17 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Council Meeting, 1969, September 8 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1969, September 9-10 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1969, September 9-10 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1969, September 9-10 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1969, September 9-10 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1969, September 9-10 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1969, September 9-10 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [1 of 2], 1969, September 9-10 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [2 of 2], 1969, September 9-10 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Transamerican and Western Cases Meeting, 1969, September 10 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Council Meeting, 1969, December 8 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1969, December 9 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1969, December 9 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [1 of 2], 1969, December 9 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [2 of 2], 1969, December 9 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1969, December 9-10 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1969, December 9-10 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1969, December 9-10 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1969, December 9-10 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1969, December 10 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Case #166 Meeting, 1969, December 15 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1970, June 9 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1970, June 9 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1970, June 9 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1970, June 9 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1970, June 9-10 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 4], 1970, June 9-11 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 4], 1970, June 9-11 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [3 of 4], 1970, June 9-11 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [4 of 4], 1970, June 9-11 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Changes of Operation Conference Meeting [1 of 2], 1970, June 23 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Changes of Operation Conference Meeting [2 of 2], 1970, June 23 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Council Meeting, 1970, September 21 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1970, September 22-23 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1970, September 22-23 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1970, September 22-23 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1970, September 22-23 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1970, September 22-23 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1970, September 22-23 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [1 of 2], 1970, September 22-23 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [2 of 2], 1970, September 22-23 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Transamerican Cases Meeting, 1970, September 23 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Special Meeting, 1970, November 17 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Council Meeting, 1971, January 25 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1971, January 26-27 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1971, January 26-27 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1971, January 26-27 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [1 of 2], 1971, January 26-27 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [2 of 2], 1971, January 26-27 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Council Meeting, 1971, January 27 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1971, January 27 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- Western Transportation Cases Meeting, 1971, January 27 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 4], 1971, January 26-28 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 4], 1971, January 26-28 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [3 of 4], 1971, January 26-28 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [4 of 4], 1971, January 26-28 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1971, January 26-29 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1971, January 26-29 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1971, January 26-29 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Council Meeting, 1971, March 8 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1971, March 9 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1971, March 9-10 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1971, March 9-10 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1971, March 9-10 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1971, March 9-10 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting, 1971, March 9-10 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1971, March 9-10 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Committee Special Meeting, 1971, April 13 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Council Meeting, 1971, June 7 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1971, June 8 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1971, June 8-9 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1971, June 8-9 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting, 1971, June 8-9 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1971, June 8-9 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1971, June 8-9 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1971, June 8-9 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1971, June 8-9 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1971, June 8-9 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Council Meeting, 1971, September 20 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1971, September 20-21 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1971, September 20-21 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1971, September 21-22 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1971, September 21-22 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1971, September 21-22 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1971, September 21-22 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [1 of 2], 1971, September 21-22 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [2 of 2], 1971, September 21-22 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1971, October 22 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Council Meeting, 1971, December 6 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [1 of 2], 1971, December 7-8 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [2 of 2], 1971, December 7-8 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1971, December 7-8 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1971, December 7-8 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1971, December 8 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1971, December 7-9 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1971, December 7-9 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Council Meeting, 1972, March 6 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1972, March 7-8 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1972, March 7-8 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1972, March 7-8 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1972, March 7-8 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1972, March 7-8 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1972, March 7-8 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1972, March 7-8 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [1 of 2], 1972, March 7-8 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [2 of 2], 1972, March 7-8 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1972, March 8 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Council Meeting, 1972, June 5 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [1 of 2], 1972, June 6 (Box 75, Folder 7)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [2 of 2], 1972, June 6 (Box 75, Folder 8)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1972, June 6 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1972, June 6-7 (Box 76, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1972, June 6-7 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1972, June 6-7 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1972, June 7-8 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1972, June 7-8 (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Council Meeting, 1972, September 18 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1972, September 19 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1972, September 19 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1972, September 19 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting, 1972, September 19 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1972, September 19 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1972, September 19-20 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1972, September 19-20 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1972, September 19-20 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- Council Meeting, 1972, December 11 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting, 1972, December 12 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1972, December 12 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1972, December 12-13 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1972, December 12-13 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1972, December 12-13 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1972, December 12-13 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1972, December 12-13 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- Conference Meeting, 1973, February 1 (Box 78, Folder 9)
- Council Meeting, 1973, March 26 (Box 78, Folder 10)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1973, March 27-28 (Box 78, Folder 11)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1973, March 27-28 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1973, March 27-28 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1973, March 27-28 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1973, March 27-28 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1973, March 27-28 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1973, March 28 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- Council Meeting, 1973, September 17 (Box 79, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Meeting [1 of 2], 1973, September 18 (Box 79, Folder 8)
- Local Cartage Meeting [2 of 2], 1973, September 18 (Box 79, Folder 9)
- Iron and Steel Meeting, 1973, September 18-19 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Meeting, 1973, September 18-19 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1973, September 18-20 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1973, September 18-20 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- Special Iron and Steel Meeting, 1973, September 20 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- Council Meeting, 1973, December 17 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Meeting [1 of 2], 1973, December 18-19 (Box 80, Folder 7)
- Change of Operations Meeting [2 of 2], 1973, December 18-19 (Box 80, Folder 8)
- Iron and Steel Meeting, 1973, December 18-19 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Meeting [1 of 2], 1973, December 18-19 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Meeting [2 of 2], 1973, December 18-19 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1973, December 19-20 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1973, December 19-20 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- Council Meeting, 1974, March 18 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1974, March 19 (Box 81, Folder 7)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1974, March 19-20 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1974, March 19-20 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1974, March 19-20 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting, 1974, March 19-20 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1974, March 19-20 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Council Meeting, 1974, June 3 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1974, June 4 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1974, June 4-5 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Competitive Review and Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1974, June 4-5 (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1974, June 4-5 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1974, June 4-5 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Council Meeting, 1974, September 16 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1974, September 17 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Iron and Steel Meeting, 1974, September 17-18 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Meeting, 1974, September 17-18 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1974, September 17-18 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1974, September 17-18 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- Council Meeting, 1974, December 9 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1974, December 10 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1974, December 10 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Committee Meeting, 1974, December 10-11 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1974, December 10-11 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1974, December 10-11 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1974, December 10-11 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1974, December 11 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Council Meeting, 1975, March 17 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1975, March 18 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1975, March 18 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [1 of 2], 1975, March 18-19 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [2 of 2], 1975, March 18-19 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1975, March 18-19 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1975, March 18-19 (Box 85, Folder 7)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1975, March 18-20 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1975, March 19 (Box 86, Folder 2)